Hey, who is that?
Eun Seo, Yoon Eun Seo
She is your sister. Isn't she cute?
Jun Seo, I will be right back.
Stay right here and wait for me.
I will be right back. Good boy.
What?
Kid, you can't play around here.
You dropped them all.
(Im Kyung Ha)
(Kim Soon Im)
(Episode 1)
(To. Jun Seo)
Yoon Jun Seo, you mean boy!
Yoon Jun Seo, what are you doing here?
Did you throw this letter in the trash?
I am sorry. I didn't mean to.
I couldn't give it back
since there was no name on it.
Do you hate me?
I like someone else.
What is it now?
This.
Don't ever do this again.
Hey, how did it go?
Tell us already.
- I want to know.
- How did it go?
What is that? Is this from us?
How did it happen?
No way.
- It is soaked.
- No.
What do we do?
He did not even read the letter.
It's all wet.
- Really?
- He is so mean.
How could he do this?
Jun Seo, wait for me.
Jun Seo.
I can't ride bikes well.
I did something today
that my brother hates.
I feel a little sorry, to be honest.
But I think it is a bit unfair.
I can't say "No" when my senior
asks a favor.
If he doesn't want to get love letters,
he should make a girlfriend.
I am the only one to get bothered.
No, it doesn't bother me.
It never bothers me at all.
I just want you to look at me.
I absolve you from your sins.
You should've done it earlier.
By the way, who is she?
Who?
You said you like someone. Who is she?
Stop it.
Who is that?
It's a secret. What's it to you?
Don't you dare tell Mom and Dad
about what happened today.
That's my decision to make.
Yoon Eun Seo.
I do what I want to.
You...
All right.
Let's play rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, let's do it.
I am ready. Let's do it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I lost again.
This is so strange. Why do I always lose?
You always make a Rock.
It is raining.
When is it going to stop raining?
It's all right. It's a shower.
I am soaked. It got heavier.
What are you doing?
It's fine.
No one is passing by,
and I have my underskirt on.
An underskirt?
Since when have you worn that?
I am in middle school now.
What are you looking at?
Goodness.
So does your brother like someone?
Yes, he said it's a secret.
Do you have anyone you like?
I do.
For real? Who is he?
Who is he? Do I know him?
Jun Seo.
What? Come on!
Let me see.
When did you grow up this much?
I don't know.
Do I look like you?
What?
Now it's your turn.
Eun Seo, when you go to college,
if you have someone you like,
you should let me know first.
Of course.
I think you are going to be rich.
- How come?
- You have thick earlobes.
So did your grandmother.
Really?
Mine are thin.
Are they? Let me see.
They were thick before.
When did they become thinner?
I am probably not your daughter.
I don't even look like you.
You might have adopted me.
What?
My precious Eun Seo.
I am stuffed.
Mom, I ate too much.
Eat more.
So that your breasts grow faster.
Mom.
Honey, our daughter is already...
Already?
Mom, please.
Her breasts.
- Her breasts?
Let me see.
No. I don't want that.
- What do you want to see?
- Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
- Mom, stop him.
- Come here.
Sit down and stop making a fuss.
- Come here now.
- No.
If I were to be reelected class president
for the second semester,
I can't promise that
we will have no more homework.
But I can promise you that
I will do my best...
to serve all of you.
What do you think?
"He would say it's great."
That's what you thought, isn't it?
"I will never tell her."
"I will be a class president to beat him."
You thought so, right?
"Choi Sin Ae should beat her."
Choi Sin Ae?
You don't know her.
She is my rival.
Your rival? Does she bother you?
No.
Jun Seo.
Seventh grade? Did you come to see me?
- Yes.
- What is it?
We came to ask you for a favor.
Your painting hangs near the front door.
I like it a lot.
So?
I am participating in an exhibition
of illustrated poems.
I wonder
if you could paint something for me.
Have we met before?
What?
No.
Then, why would I have to
paint it for you?
I am pretty busy these days. I am sorry.
Sin Ae.
Choi Sin Ae.
Wait.
Is her name Choi Sin Ae?
Yes.
So, are you in Class Two?
And Yoon Eun Seo.
Hold on, Choi Sin Ae.
Yoon Eun Seo.
Choi Sin Ae.
And the last one.
Yoon Eun Seo.
So, that makes 29 votes for Yoon Eun Seo
and 16 votes for Choi Sin Ae.
Our class president
for the second semester is Yoon Eun Seo.
And the vice president is Choi Sin Ae.
Congratulations.
Give them a round of applause!
And at the first exam
in the second semester,
we won first place.
And Choi Sin Ae is
at the top of the whole school.
Congratulations. You did a great job.
You know there will be an illustrated poem
exhibition next month, right?
Yes.
Korean literature teacher has recommended
Yoon Eun Seo and Choi Sin Ae,
I think...
It might be better if Eun Seo does it.
Choi Sin Ae already participated in it
in the first semester!
And Eun Seo has her brother
to help her with the painting.
Isn't that right?
Choi Sin Ae, can you give it to her?
Yes.
Eun Seo's mother is going
to make some rice cakes this weekend,
to celebrate the fact that
we won first place.
Give her a round of applause!
I like your underskirt a lot.
I like it, too.
Do you? It is for ladies.
- Where did you get it?
- I am jealous.
"Everyone, Eun Seo's mother..."
"will make rice cakes on the weekend."
Why is Eun Seo...
the class president the whole year
when the top student is Sin Ae?
Eun Seo was voted for president.
Lee Kang Hee, you stay out of this.
Are you her handmaid or something?
What did you say?
Thanks to your prince brother,
you get to participate in the exhibition.
You must be thrilled.
You are right. I am thrilled.
You said my brother is a prince,
and I am a princess.
There is no reason not to be happy.
Thank you for calling me a princess.
You are so right.
Jun Seo is definitely a prince.
And I am a crown princess.
Let's do our best, vice president.
And Sin Ae, if you have something to say,
do it yourself.
I will be listening to you.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, there is a problem.
Your underskirt is on that tree.
Come on, hurry.
(Seventh Grade Class Two, Yoon Eun Seo)
It must be Sin Ae who did this.
I will go tell the teacher.
Don't do it.
Eun Seo.
Over there, is that Eun Seo?
Eun Seo, come down.
Come down now.
Eun Seo.
Come down.
Great job.
- Come down now.
Are you upset? Are you mad?
I am upset, too.
Please scold her, Jun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Who is it? Who did that?
I don't know.
Choi Sin Ae did that.
You have no idea how she bullies Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
- Choi Sin Ae.
- No, she didn't do it.
What do you mean she didn't?
It must have been her.
Jun Seo.
- I believe it was her.
- Kang Hee.
He doesn't even know who she is.
I guess he knows her.
Jun Seo!
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
What happened? How much did she get hurt?
Where is Eun Seo?
It was all my fault.
I should've waited for her.
It happened because I left her alone...
It was all my fault.
She was injured severely.
She needs surgery.
What should I do?
How long will the surgery take?
You needn't worry too much.
She will get some scars,
but she will be fine.
There might be blood loss.
So can I get some blood samples?
- I will do it.
- No, I will do it.
Who has Type B blood?
What?
Your daughter has Type B blood.
No way. Her blood type should be O.
Both of our blood types are O.
What?
Are you sure you are not mistaken?
If so, you cannot have a child
with Type B blood.
Test your blood type again, please.
Why do we have to test blood types again?
Thank you for waiting. I have the results.
It shows that your blood type is O,
and yours is, too.
So, if both of our blood types are O,
our child cannot have Type B blood?
Yes, that is right.
Are there any exceptions?
That is impossible.
Honey.
What is going on?
Did something happen to Eun Seo?
No, nothing happened. Don't worry.
Let's wait.
Honey,
do say something.
I should not have come home.
I need to be there when Eun Seo wakes up.
I should go back.
You or Jun Seo can bring her clothes.
Talk with me.
About what?
There is nothing to talk about.
The blood type.
Our blood types.
You and I, we both have Type O blood.
So what?
Don't you know your blood type?
Honey, Eun Seo's blood type is B.
So, what about it?
What is the matter with that?
Eun Seo...
Eun Seo might not be our daughter.
No.
Yoon Eun Seo.
Looking at you being on a bed like this,
I am scared you might not wake up.
Did it hurt a lot?
I am sorry I hurt you.
I am so sorry.
I absolve you from your sins.
Yoon Eun Seo.
You were going to apologize
while I was asleep,
and never apologize again,
isn't that right?
How did you know?
Were Mom and Dad startled a lot?
Of course.
Mom went home to pick up your clothes.
She will be back tomorrow morning.
What about you?
I couldn't leave you alone.
No, I mean, are you startled, too?
No.
You are mean. I am disappointed in you.
I thought my heart had stopped.
I absolve you from your sins.
Are you really?
It hurts.
- Did it hurt?
- I will tell mom about it.
I am not talking to you.
I have been thinking.
If our child has been switched
at the hospital,
Eun Seo is my daughter.
Something is wrong. It has to be.
My Eun Seo is my daughter.
What if she is not?
What if there is another daughter?
Honey.
I don't know anything at all.
I don't want to hear anything.
I'm not going to listen to what you say.
There were two babies born on that day.
From Ms. Im Kyung Ha
and from Ms. Kim Soon Im.
The blood we took from the infants
when they were born...
Ms. Im Kyung Ha's baby had Type O blood,
and Ms. Kim Soon Im's baby
had Type B blood.
Was it O?
Yes, according to the medical records.
One is O, and the other is B.
If your daughter's blood type is B,
the baby seems to have been
switched afterward.
- Hey!
- Please let it go.
Please let it go. Nurse.
Please calm down.
Choi Sin Ae.
Can I paint the picture
for your exhibition?
- Why?
- Let me do it.
You said you liked my paintings.
Did Eun Seo ask you to do it?
Besides, after this,
I want you to stop bullying Eun Seo.
Stop bullying her?
Do you take me for a gangster?
If you aren't one,
stop bothering my sister.
If you bother her again,
I won't just let you off easy.
But I am asking you to end this
with my painting for you.
Do you understand?
That's funny,
who'd like those paintings...
Then don't you think you should ask me
rather than threaten me?
I will think about it
if you ask me on your knees.
Are you happy now?
Don't bother Eun Seo from now on.
Is there a place called
"Sun San Jib" here?
Yes, go that way and then over there.
Hey!
Why are you making so much fuss
for touching your butt once?
I will never come back here.
Hey, you jerk!
You rude man.
I may be a widow,
but my buttocks are not for a drunkard
like you to touch.
Hey, you bastard!
What would you like to have?
We only have hot soup with rice.
How can I help you?
You don't look like people
who'd have a meal in this kind of a place.
We came here for your daughter.
What about my daughter?
Are you teachers from her school?
Did she do something wrong?
No, we are not.
Your daughter's date of birth is
October Fourth, isn't it?
How did you know that?
Didn't you give birth at Ga Ram Hospital?
Who on earth are you two?
Can we meet your daughter?
What is going on here?
Honey!
I don't want to meet her.
I am not going to meet her ever.
You tricked me into taking me here.
You did not mention
we were going to meet her.
Honey, think through it reasonably.
What is going on?
I will go to Eun Seo.
Honey, why are you acting like this?
Why are you doing this?
Can't you hear me?
What is it?
What is wrong with you
coming to my house and making a fuss?
Stop yelling. You don't know anything.
What did you just say?
Our children were switched.
Honey.
Our daughter was switched with yours.
We came here from the hospital.
Honey.
Let's go to the hospital.
Go home first.
Go to the hospital.
Please take me to Eun Seo.
How can you be so cruel like that?
How could you do that to me and Eun Seo?
- What?
- You stay.
I will go alone.
Mom.
Eun Seo.
Why did you come?
I told you that you don't need to.
It is raining.
You are scared when it rains.
I will protect you.
I'm not a child.
Are you not mom's baby anymore?
I will keep you safe.
So no one can touch you.
I will protect you.
Mom?
Eun Seo, my daughter.
I will watch every moment
of you growing up.
When you go to high school,
when you have someone you like in college,
I will choose your wedding dress
when you get married.
I will hold your hands
in your bridal suite.
When you have a baby, I...
Mom?
Eun Seo, should we secretly order
black bean sauce noodles?
Really? Yes.
Hey, who is that?
Eun Seo, Yoon Eun Seo.
She is your sister. Isn't she cute?
Stay right here and wait for me.
I will be right back. Good boy.
Honey.
Why are you up?
- How is Eun Seo?
- She is good.
Where is Jun Seo?
Wait for me.
I will be back after taking some pictures.
What?
Kid, you can't play around here.
You dropped them all.
(Im Kyung Ha)
(Kim Soon Im)
Let's get out of here.
Jun Seo, why are you there?
Come here.
Let's go.
Your dad died.
Poor thing, you didn't even meet your dad.
It's fine.
It would be better not to have
a father like that.
Our daughter was switched with yours.
The house was terrible.
Her mother was, too.
Everything is so messed up.
I am sorry.
I...
Eun Seo and you,
I love you more than anything.
I know that.
But,
thinking of her living in that house...
Honey,
let's leave to be an exchange professor.
Before it is too late,
before something terrible happens,
let's go to the U.S.,
putting everything behind us,
and live with Jun Seo and Eun Seo.
Let's do that.
I'm done.
Jun Seo.
It is so weird today.
You and mom both.
Do you want juice?
Eun Seo, I'm fine.
What is it? What's the matter?
Would you like to know a secret?
A secret?
About the person I like.
For real?
What kind of a person is she?
She is...
a bit clumsy,
stubborn,
and messy when it comes to eating.
So is she pretty?
No.
Her hair is about this long,
and she has round eyes like yours.
She is about your height.
But she is so ugly.
Ugly?
And she is a fool.
Even when I have been harsh on her,
she always follows me around.
She really bothers me.
She can't even ride a bike well.
That is me.
You made me a fool.
I'm not teasing you.
Eun Seo, if we were not siblings,
could we have crossed paths?
What?
Of course.
We are bound by fate, a weary fate.
All right,
let's play rock, paper, scissors.
If you win, we are meant to be,
and if I win, we are not.
Okay. Wait for a second.
No.
Rock, paper, scissors.
This is so strange. Why do I always lose?
You always make a Rock.
I am ready. Let's do it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
I win!
See, I told you so.
We are meant to be.
Good job, my fist.
We should tell their teachers...
that we leave for the U.S. next month.
Let's do that.
I want to leave soon.
Can you live like this?
Don't you want to meet her once?
No, I don't.
You...
No, I won't meet her.
I don't think I can go back as it was
if I see her.
I cannot give up Eun Seo.
I won't meet her.
(Eun Sol Exhibition of Illustrated Poems)
Jun Seo painted this for the student
in my class...
who replaced Eun Seo.
How grateful of him.
Of course, he has to.
I appreciate you for saying that.
I need to do something for a moment.
Why don't you look around?
- Yes, we will.
- See you later.
Excuse me.
I like the poem.
Choi Sin Ae? Who is she?
You don't need to know her.
Choi Sin Ae,
I told you about
the top student in my class.
Is that her?
Where is she?
Hello.
Is this where the exhibition
of illustrated poems is held?
Go this way.
This way? Thanks.
Mom.
Sin Ae.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you here?
I came to see your illustrated poem.
- Where is it?
- Leave now.
What if someone were to see you?
I don't care. I'll leave after seeing it.
I need to see yours.
- Where is it?
- Mom.
Hello, I am Choi Sin Ae.
Hello.
If Eun Seo is your daughter,
Sin Ae is your daughter, too.
No, Sin Ae is our actual child.
Have you ever thought about Eun Seo?
Are you going to leave Eun Seo?
Sin Ae is my only daughter.
I didn't mean...
I really wish you would disappear.
Have you ever thought
"I wish I had a father?"
Eun Seo's father whom we met before.
Why did you meet him?
I am better than Eun Seo at school,
but she is the class president
because she has better parents!
What am I?
Go with your wealthy biological parents!
Biological parents?
Sin Ae, what is going on?
Is that true?
Is it true I am your daughter?
- You and I were switched.
- Sin Ae!
I am their daughter, not you!